A Guide to the Western Fairfax County Survey Photograph Collection, 1976-1986 (bulk 1985-1986)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-29, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A6, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A6, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A6, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A6, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A6, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A6, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A6, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A6, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-30, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-31, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A9, Williams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-32, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A7, Payne House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A7, Payne House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A7, Payne House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A7, Payne House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A2, Wellert 50 House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A8, Werner Electric, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-33, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-1-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-34, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A4, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A1, Flatlick Branch Bridge, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A1, Flatlick Branch Bridge, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A1, Flatlick Branch Bridge, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-35, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-36, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-36, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-36, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-37, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 35-3-A2, Peterson Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: no site, View off West Ox Road across Franklin Farms of subdivision, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: no site, View off West Ox Road across Franklin Farms of subdivision, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: no site, View off West Ox Road across Franklin Farms of subdivision, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-38, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A14, Sams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A14, Sams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A14, Sams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A14, Sams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A14, Sams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A14, Sams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A14, Sams House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A1, Spears House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A13, Almos House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A13, Almos House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A13, Almos House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-39, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A13, Almos House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A13, Almos House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A13, Almos House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A13, Almos House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A2, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A2, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A2, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A2, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A2, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-40, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1984 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Squirrel Hill, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Taber House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Taber House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Taber House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Taber House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Taber House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Taber House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Taber House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Taber House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A12, Taber House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-41, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Harrison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-42, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A18, Frying Pan Blacksmith Shop, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A18, Frying Pan Blacksmith Shop, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-43, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: no site, [unidentified house], 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 0
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 001